Fiaz Bin Sayeed

Fast learner with a passion for finance and management. Created my own startup as a high school student and have experience working with and educating low income students Park Manor West, Mailbox #1700, Babson College **347-707-9500 fbinsayeed1@babson.edu**

EXPERIENCE

Instantpics NYC, New York — Founder

June 2017 - March 2018

Created and maintained company webpages using HTML and CSS

Created financial and marketing plans to gain new and retain existing customers

Wrote and edited business plans, fact sheets and collateral

RQM Tutorial, New York — *Educator*

August 2017 - PRESENT

Created Marketing and Budgetary plans to gain customers

Tutored 7th to 12th grade students in math proficiency

Doctor's Office, New York — *Intern*

September 2015 - July 2016

Accurately recorded treatment information in patient records

Competently prepared dental materials for patients

MSA HS Council, New York — Financial Chairperson

July 2017 - January 2018

Consulted with local business owners for fundraising

Allocated council funds in order to donate to Rohingya Relief Organizations

EDUCATION

The Bronx High School of Science, New York

September 2014 - June 2018

Graduated with Bronx Science Diploma and Advanced Regents Diploma

Babson College, Massachusetts

September 2018 (Expected to graduate in 2022) Majoring in Entrepreneurship and Finance

SKILLS

Microsoft Office, HTML, CSS, Python, Web Content, Adobe Photoshop, Social Media Marketing, 80 WPM

LANGUAGES

English, Bengali, Spanish